<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nduati Daniel</title><link>http://danielchege.me/</link><description>Recent content on Nduati Daniel</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 19:26:50 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://danielchege.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Notes 6 &amp; 7 &amp; 8</title><link>http://danielchege.me/posts/week-notes-6-7-8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 19:26:50 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://danielchege.me/posts/week-notes-6-7-8/</guid><description>This is more of a 3 weeks review, loads of transition and settling.
Week&amp;rsquo;s Quote To know what you know and what you do not know, that is true knowledge. — Confucius
Personal Got to meet the R&amp;amp;D team, really cool guys :) Love that I get to work on life-changing technology for smallholder farmers. Discovered a cool meditation app, I hope to build a habit of meditating regularly. I haven&amp;rsquo;t been actively writting code for sometime now, looking to change that.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Notes 5</title><link>http://danielchege.me/posts/week-notes-5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 07:07:16 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://danielchege.me/posts/week-notes-5/</guid><description>Week&amp;rsquo;s Quote Your growth stops the day you identify as a victim.. — Unkown
Side-projects Working on another dumb idea solely for fun. Personal Relocated to Nanyuki. :) Relocating is fun but moving stuff isn&amp;rsquo;t. Excited for the new challenge and environment. Didn&amp;rsquo;t get to write a whole lot of code this week. :( Random interesting stuff Reduce coupling in your python code How to write technical specification of an embedded product Google&amp;rsquo;s A.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Notes 4</title><link>http://danielchege.me/posts/week-notes-4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 15:46:36 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://danielchege.me/posts/week-notes-4/</guid><description>Week&amp;rsquo;s Quote Human opinions are fallible 1. — Zahid
Side-Projects You can now filter jokes by there id_range on JokesAPI Personal Got offers from the two companies I was interviewing with. yaay :) At a crossroad of which company I&amp;rsquo;ll go with, both offers are pretty sensible in their own right. Refactored my neovim config for the 1000th time lol will try to port it from vimscript to lua. Been really enjoying Go!</description></item><item><title>Weekly Notes 3</title><link>http://danielchege.me/posts/week-notes-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 22:14:09 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://danielchege.me/posts/week-notes-3/</guid><description>Week&amp;rsquo;s Quote Confusion is a feeling that precedes learning something. It means you should pay closer attention, not disengage. — Unknown
Personal My small sister turned a year older! Started interviewing with another Kenyan hardware startup. Had my first live coding interview session! The challenges were really interesting and fun to solve! Been trying to use twitter less and reducing my general social media consumption. Barcelona has really been playing good football lately.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Notes 2</title><link>http://danielchege.me/posts/week-notes-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 23:42:09 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://danielchege.me/posts/week-notes-2/</guid><description> Week&amp;rsquo;s Quote Each day gives us a sunrise and a sunset. Often, that is enough. — Unknown
Personal Been learning some Rust and Go on and off. Binged an unhealthy amount of &amp;ldquo;Mordern Family&amp;rdquo;. Not a very productive week for me overall. Random interesting stuff The ThePrimeagen&amp;rsquo;s video: Is ADHD Bad For Programming? Learning Go as a Python Developer: The Good and the Bad Theo&amp;rsquo;s developer goals video.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Notes 1</title><link>http://danielchege.me/posts/week-notes-1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 15:46:34 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://danielchege.me/posts/week-notes-1/</guid><description>Week&amp;rsquo;s Quote What I cannot create, I do not understand. — Richard Feynman
Open Source Work Made my first open source contribution to hugo-coder the theme that this website is built on. The PR though just a doc link fix, got reviewed and merged. Personal I&amp;rsquo;ve commited to writting a weekly-review of stuff I do or happens to me over each week, and which I find interesting enough to write about.</description></item><item><title>Hello, world!</title><link>http://danielchege.me/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 21:14:18 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://danielchege.me/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>Welcome to my blog. This is my little corner of the web where I will post content on code, tech and stuff that interests me.</description></item><item><title>Hi! I'm Daniel</title><link>http://danielchege.me/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://danielchege.me/about/</guid><description>I build and break stuff, with a focus on embedded systems, firmware development, and software development. I enjoy problem solving and working on impactful projects. I am on a perpetual learning journey and I&amp;rsquo;m constantly exploring new challenges and opportunities to grow.
When I&amp;rsquo;m not listening to music, tinkering with electronics, or writing code, you can catch me on the football field, enjoying/ the beautiful game.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>http://danielchege.me/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://danielchege.me/contact/</guid><description>Reach out to me via Mail or Mobile</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>http://danielchege.me/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://danielchege.me/projects/</guid><description>Nothing to see here yet :(</description></item></channel></rss>