<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Daniel Nduati</title><link>/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Daniel Nduati</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 22:14:09 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Notes 3</title><link>/posts/week-notes-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 22:14:09 +0300</pubDate><guid>/posts/week-notes-3/</guid><description>Week&amp;rsquo;s Quote Confusion is a feeling that precedes learning something. It means you should pay closer attention, not disengage. — Unknown
Personal My small sister turned a year older! Started interviewing with another Kenyan hardware startup. Had my first live coding interview session! The challenges were really interesting and fun to solve! Been trying to use twitter less and reducing my general social media consumption. Barcelona has really been playing good football lately.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Notes 2</title><link>/posts/week-notes-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 23:42:09 +0300</pubDate><guid>/posts/week-notes-2/</guid><description> Week&amp;rsquo;s Quote Each day gives us a sunrise and a sunset. Often, that is enough. — Unknown
Personal Been learning some Rust and Go on and off. Binged an unhealthy amount of &amp;ldquo;Mordern Family&amp;rdquo;. Not a very productive week for me overall. Random interesting stuff The ThePrimeagen&amp;rsquo;s video: Is ADHD Bad For Programming? Learning Go as a Python Developer: The Good and the Bad Theo&amp;rsquo;s developer goals video.</description></item><item><title>LinkedIn Api with Python</title><link>/posts/linkedin-api-python/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 15:35:28 +0300</pubDate><guid>/posts/linkedin-api-python/</guid><description>Introduction LinkedIn is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest professional network on the internet. You can use LinkedIn to find the right job or internship, connect and strengthen professional relationships, and learn the skills you need to succeed in your career. LinkedIn provides an API interface that enables its partners and developers build, run, and grow sustainable businesses on the platform. An API, or Application Programming Interface, is a way of communication between various software components.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Notes 1</title><link>/posts/week-notes-1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 15:46:34 +0300</pubDate><guid>/posts/week-notes-1/</guid><description>Week&amp;rsquo;s Quote What I cannot create, I do not understand. — Richard Feynman
Open Source Work Made my first open source contribution to hugo-coder the theme that this website is built on. The PR though just a doc link fix, got reviewed and merged. Personal I&amp;rsquo;ve commited to writting a weekly-review of stuff I do or happens to me over each week, and which I find interesting enough to write about.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with Fast API and Docker</title><link>/posts/fastapi-docker/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 18:33:35 +0300</pubDate><guid>/posts/fastapi-docker/</guid><description>APIs and FastAPI Creating APIs, or application programming interfaces, is an important part of making your software accessible to a broad range of users. FastAPI is a high-performance API based on Pydantic and Starlette. It is an awesome modern Python framework designed to enable developers to quickly build robust and high performance APIs.
Why FastAPI? Some of the really cool features of fast api can be found in the frameworks official website.</description></item><item><title>Hello, world!</title><link>/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 21:14:18 +0300</pubDate><guid>/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>Welcome to my blog. This is my little corner of the web where I will post content on code, tech and stuff that interests me.</description></item></channel></rss>